# **Phạm Viết Long**

Software Developer



## **Profile**

- **18/12/2003**
- Male
- 0368353613
- phmvtlong@gmail.com
- github.com/daylapvlong
- Hanoi

#### **Skills**

#### Front-end development

Sufficeent in HTML&CSS framework such as ReactJS, Tailwind with extensive knowledge on Javascript.

#### **Back-end development**

Capable of developing NodeJS and Java Spring Boot application to certain extends.

# **Communication & Teamwork**

Competented in project management, setting up weekly team meetings to discuss progress and challenges and developed project proposals, reports, and documentation in university projects.

#### **Public speaking**

Experienced speaker and Master of Ceremonies (MC) in serveral events held by Japanese Software Engineering Club .

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a software engineer with 2 years of education and experience in the field. My applied skills include both Front end and Back end development such as React, Tailwind, NodeJS, Java Spring Boot. I also have a solid English background with a 7.0 IELTS certificate and some others soft skills like Public Speaking, Tutoring and Event Organizing.

#### **Education**

## **FPT University**

2022 - Now

Software Engineering

- Demonstrated understanding in various software development methodologies
- Conducted comprehensive research on multiple software development models, enabling efficient project management
- Applied modern software development tools and techniques to enhance productivity and streamline the software development process.

# Work experience

#### **IGS IELTS Center**

2022 - Now

**IELTS Tutor** 

- Help developed effective communication skills and learned how to empower others to achieve their goals.
- Acquired valuable insights into time management and documentation processes.
- Honed my language skills and expanded my linguistic repertoire.

## **Activities**

#### **Japanese Software Engineering Club**

2022 - Now

Academic Depariment

- Actively engaged in various programming events and competitions facilitated by JS Club, including CodeTour, The Coding Project, CodeFest and etc..
- Demonstrated proficiency in software engineering by being appointed as the speaker of TechTalk, a recurring talkshow that delves into the latest technological developments and their applications.

## **Certifications**

2020 7.0 IELTS certificate

2020 Microsoft Office Specialist Expert - Office Word

2021 Microsoft Office Specialist Expert - Office PowerPoint